pimpmysearch.com 2009-03-19

# Pimp My Search - Privacy Policy

* * *

**[Pimp My Search](http://www.pimpmysearch.com/) \- Privacy Policy**

Welcome to Pimp My Search, a Fun Novelty site where you can create your own Personalized search engine. We take your privacy very seriously. To make it easier for you to read and understand our privacy policy, we did the unconventional thing - we wrote this in plain English and tried to keep it to a reasonably short length.

**Information Collected   & Usage**  
When you use Pimp My Search, you may submit personally identifiable information such as your name. We also collect other non-personally identifiable data, which may include your IP address, browser type etc. We also use your non-personally identifiable data information to measure our website traffic and performance. 

**Children**  
Children under the age of thirteen (13) are not eligible to use our service. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. They provide us with data that we can use to improve the quality of our service and make it easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so.

**Security**  
We use industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us.

**Effective Date**   
This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on Jan 27, 2009. 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**  
From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. Your continued usage of PimpMySearch constitutes an acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms of Service so we encourage you to visit this page periodically to review any changes.

**Contact**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, you can [contact us here](http://pimpmysearch.com/contact.php)

_Note: Pimp My Search   is a non-commercial novelty site, not related to Google._

© 2009 PimpMySearch.com
